Stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
The paint within brings
out a map of your own.
To the left and the right,
all we saw stormy nights.
All the rough winds and
waves coming day after day.
And the values we had
were about to collapse.
Oh, just where do we go next?
And as we look down to the compass in
hand Is it showing us the right direction?
All we know is nobody
here knows it for certain.
So close your eyes and breathe in deeply.
And listen to your soul.
You'll see a path in front of you.
And you'll know just where you need to go.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make us stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
I'll do it my own way,
that's what's best for me.
And you do it your way,
that's how it's got to be.
We're moving forward, now I'm ready.
But at times it's okay
to get help on the way.
For the future ahead, burning bright.
For what's ahead you see.
Is beyond your wildest dreams.
So stand up tall, reach out your hand.
Cut through the wind and make a stand.
Don't let the darkness
win, just break through.
We'll do it our way,
the best that we know.
With tears and doubts and tone.
We'll go where we all wanna go.
The page within brings colors of our own.
I'll make you nice and toasty.
I'll make you nice and crispy.
I'll make you nice and bloody.
Ma-ma-ma-ma...
Please take me straight
to the inner castle.
You're making me fly you
around when I'm injured, huh?
This better be important.
I'm just worried.
Hopefully it's nothing.
But the Beast Pirate
said that some sort of
giant apparition appeared
on the second floor.
What does that mean for us?
It's spreading fire through the castle.
Be ready for the worst. Always.
Run away!
The monster's coming!
The Ten Samurai are blocking the exit!
We're stuck! Step back! We got a cannon!
The fire is spreading everywhere!
Secure an escape route!
They're through those samurai!
Hurry!
Let's get out of here
or we'll burn to death!
I'm telling you, young
master, it's a sweet deal!
Hear me out for a sec!
You won't regret it, I swear!
Moving on to the next
target, you little weasel.
I don't buy into your plans
so you suck up the Yamato.
Young master!
Stop the poo!
I told you I have somewhere to be!
Stop following me!
Fuga, Fuga!
Sorry, Fuga.
I didn't mean to yell at you
back there, but I'm in a hurry!
Fuga, Fuga!
I sure wish I could be as carefree as you.
This is an urgent report
for all castle floors.
The giant plane creature is
currently headed for the basement.
Huh?
A cushion? Not quite.
They're hairs, but I don't know whose.
Well, that's odd. Fugle?
Are you ready?
Ready.
Don't move!
It seems we have to fight!
Fight!
Uh...
Robin?
What is that thing?
A ball of flames.
What a nuisance.
What the hell?
It's mute!
The slave creature's
intentions are still unknown.
Brother, run! It's coming! Hold on!
Right now, it's descending through
the floors at a steady pace.
It seems impervious to attack.
Take extreme caution!
He's pulling his crust.
Is he trying to make fun of me?
What the hell is this?
Ready!
Impurious Deepline State!
I hit like a laser beam!
It's impossible to block!
In ancient times, this is
how Pteranodons hunted.
And now, you're my prey!
Damn, I don't know my dinosaurs.
I gotta hit him with something
or he's just gonna wear me down.
So, I'm guessing that flame on your back
must be a Pteranodon thing, too, huh?
That's stupid.
Hey, you're the one
with the stupid powers!
He's just gonna keep trash-talking
till he picks me off.
It's time to knock that
bastard out of the sky.
Three-sword style, black
rope, great Tatsumaki!
That didn't even leave a dent.
What the hell is he made of?
So, dinosaurs have skin tough as steel.
Just like dragons, huh?
I have far more than just tough skin.
My powers are unique.
I'll give you a sword fight if you want.
I do enjoy a good duel.
I cut him, but he doesn't bleed.
Drunk Tiger!
His wings are strong.
They're agile too.
Seems like he uses them
more to attack than fly.
The flame on his back keeps burning.
I thought that was part of his
Devil Fruit power, but maybe not.
He could be a fishman, a parked
giant, or anything under that mask.
Hell, he might even be
something I've never heard of.
I see confusion in your eyes.
You're looking for an answer.
This is not good.
I have to think.
If I can't figure him out.
I'm screwed.
There's no way I can beat him like this.
What's that sound?
Show me something.
I must be hearing things.
What the hell's going on?
Ah, damn it, Enmo!
Hmm? Music?
Someone is playing a
charme scene, but why?
This is a battleground.
This is hell.
It's coming from the room
next door Is it an enemy?
Who is it?
The banquet is over.
They should be running for their lives!
It's too bright.
I can't see.
It can't be.
Toborosaki!
I'm dreaming, aren't I?
Either that or I'm dead.
I've thought about you every
night since that terrible day.
You've never left my mind
for an instant, my dear.
Nor have you left my mind, my lord.
I promise I will be by your
side until the very end.
If this is a dream, I
don't want to wake up!
What is that?
It's moving through the walls.
Into the abyss...
Into the abyss!
Shoot it!
This is a message to all fours!
The flame creature is continuing
its descent to the basement!
The fire is spreading along
with it, so make caution!
A flame creature?
And it's headed down!
At this rate, it'll reach
the armory before me.
This is about to be a disaster.
It's going to set off
all of those explosives.
I have to hurry.
Fuga!
Can you help me with something, please?
Fuga! This way!
Just follow me! Fuga!
If I had it my way,
I'd take a nap in this fellow's hair
and wake up when this disaster is over.
But life's not so simple, is it?
We've bought some time,
but they can't be far.
Then they'll be after us soon.
We should hurry.
There's nowhere to run.
We'll catch you soon enough.
Give me a smile.
You'll be front page news.
Lapdogs of the Celestial Dragon
spotted at Kaido's castle.
Now that's a scoop, boy!
One little call to Morgan's and this
pirate's gonna be rolling in the dome.
Ooh, yeah, ooh, ooh, that's a good sign.
Well, I can see it now.
After losing their arms brokered
Doflamingo, the government makes their play.
Hey, Apoo!
Diaz Drake.
I know exactly who you are
and what you're trying to do.
Then you'd better cook up
a damn good cover story.
How inconvenient.
I'll erase you.
You're welcome.
That hurt!
Bunch of pugs!
You stinking assassins can suck it!
I thought for sure they
struck you dead. Oh, shut up!
I got Armament Haki just
like anyone else, okay?
They're gonna pay for screwing with me!
I can't believe I just saved some
dumbass traitor from the Navy.
Stop yapping.
Are you gonna end this, or is it all me?
End it?
I didn't even start it, man!
Yes, you did.
These guys suck.
You better believe I'll fight.
No!
No! Bk-bk-bk!
Why is this happening?
Hey, Enma!
I didn't say you could unleash your power!
You listen to me!
How sad.
Happy of falling out.
what are you staring at I'll give you one
chance now show me your
worst you ask for it
Jackpaw. What?
Sorry to eavesdrop, but you were talking
to the pirate hunter, weren't you?
That guy's never going
to be king, by the way.
That was close.
I'd be dead if I didn't
use my armament in Haki.
That was one hell of an explosion.
Was he planning on dying with me?
That looked like a suicide attack.
except he doesn't have a scratch on him.
King is a Lunarian, a race that was
thought to have gone extinct long ago.
They're monsters who are able to
survive in all natural environments.
In the past, they were known as gods if
you want an idea of how strong they are.
If they're so special, why
did they become extinct?
I am a scientist!
Not a history kick!
One sword style. E .I.
Death.
I am some.
Oh, my God.
I didn't face him at all.
I keep ramping up, but you
don't even bother to block.
The music again.
Oh, Emma, wait!
Hear your deep pride! Stay!
Jakuna can be killed!
A swordsman getting held
back by his own sword.
Now that's a sight.
The sword's cursed I think I'll take it.
No I can't sell it because
if something happens to you
with that sword the curse could
come back to me you idiot.
Yeah then how's this
we'll play a little game?
Yeah, I'll take it.
I see you've become quite adept. Huh?
Seems as though Enma
has met a worthy owner.
You already wield Kitetsu III.
Well, that's one of mine, too.
You've got to be kidding.
Are you really going to
die to save your sword?
It burns!
It didn't fall.
That's one good thing.
Waro Ichimonji.
Sensei, I ask that you
let me have her sword.
Alright, it's yours then.
I promise I'll get stronger
for both of us, Kuina.
I'll be so strong that my name
reaches up to the heavens.
I'll be the world's greatest
swordsman, no matter what it takes.
Boy,
have you not questioned
why the famed blade Lady
Hiyori left you feel so
comfortable in your hand?
It works much like a cursive blade does.
The weak cannot handle them.
Though there is a much bigger reason why
it feels familiar to you as you wield it.
You may find this shocking,
but your Wado Ichimonji and Enma
were crafted by the very same man.
He was the legendary
blacksmith Shimoski Kozaburo.
I never thought to question
this sword's origin.
But how did a blade from
the land of Wano end
up in the east blue in
the middle of nowhere?
Oh, my God.
Got all your swords back, go!
The Imperial Slings and Arrows!
Enma!
A sword from the land of Wano.
Zorojuro.
The word Tsunachi.
Okiku advised me against using it.
It's just a saying.
Some old guy from my
village told me years back.
Can't really say I've used it myself.
That old man from the village.
He was always sitting by
himself looking at the sea.
I didn't even know his name.
But he told me all these things
Sonachi, it is a word that means good
luck and can uplift your spirits.
Huh?
My spirits are doing fine, thanks.
I don't need any weird tricks.
So anyway, I wanted to ask you,
did you used to be a samurai?
Because that's what everyone
at the dojo is saying.
Then tell them to shut up.
If word gets out, then the
Navy's gonna come knocking.
I don't get it.
The Navy?
I'm done talking.
Go home, you little shit.
What's your deal, you old weirdo?
Dojo kick you out, or are you just bored?
I came here to get some
more sword practice.
Kuina kicked my butt,
like she always does.
Huh?
But I can't pay for these.
You can have them.
They're blunt, though.
A damn shame.
Everything I make these days turns out
like that, but they're fine for practice
Listen up kid a sword is not a knife.
It's made to kill people.
It's an instrument of
death and nothing else
The job of a swordsmith is to make
their blades as deadly as possible.
We deal in murder.
Every sword has its own personality
and some are quite willful.
It's a swordsman's job to tame them.
If a sword is too dangerous,
people say it's cursed.
What a load of crap!
That's a sign of quality.
Only the weak fear it.
A swordsman bends it to his will.
Calling it cursed is a badge of honor.
Swords should be terrifying.
Their only purpose is to take lives.
After all, they yearn for it.
There was a sword that
I made when I was young.
A true masterpiece.
In all my years since, I've
never been able to top it.
The sword had a stern personality.
When you held it in your hand,
it set a shiver down your spine.
That's how fine a blade it was.
It's named after the great
king who presides over hell.
The great king who presides over hell.
The village was named Shemotski.
That can't be a coincidence.
I didn't know until the
day that old man died,
but it turns out he was
Kouina's grandfather.
If you want me to give your famed
blade back, you got to catch me.
It's not a famed blade.
It's just a practice sword.
Hey, guys, I heard something crazy. Huh?
This will blow your mind.
My grandma told me this village
was founded by a pirate.
What?
A pirate, huh?
He was the legendary
blacksmith Shemotsuki Kozaburo.
He broke the laws of this
country and took off.
Last anyone saw him was 50 years back.
That old man was a samurai
from the land of Wano.
The famous blacksmith,
Shemotsuki Kozaburo.
Fine swords watch us humans closely.
Maybe they're looking
for the right partner.
They're patient.
But in the end, they say
the sword chooses the owner.
You chose me.
You came to me because
you wanted to test me.
The sword doesn't have malice.
It isn't doing this to harm me.
Guess that means my
power is still lacking.
Odin willed you with ease, even though
you took away so much Haki from me.
I wish I could have seen that.
All right, Enma.
One more round.
We got him now!
The pirate hunter's going down!
The bastard's in bad shape!
Master King!
I'm begging you!
We want a shot at Zero Two!
This is our chance!
We take him out, we'll get promoted!
Me first, I'll finish him!
How should I do this?
I need to stabilize my Haki.
I'm releasing too much.
I'll die if I keep this up.
No!
That's it.
I see.
Fancy yourself a conqueror, huh?
Yeah, okay.
The world's greatest swordsman, huh?
Well, when it comes to crewmates,
as the next king of the pirates,
I'll need the best.
Whatever it takes.
After all, I made a promise to my captain.
My captain and best friend.